Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 19 (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
    - RSU (oreg) THE CASE AGAINST ROTC by Howard Dratch and James Roven, self wrs (11) pp. Illustrated.
    - RSU (org). RALLY THURSDAY NOON / PROTEST CHEMICAL BIOLOGICAL WAR RESEARCH!
    - Scholarship, Education and Defense fund for Racial Equality (org). DEAR FRIEND.= open letter from Julian Bond, headed THE NEW CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT / A Timely Messagewith contribution envelope.
    - SDS (campus) PROGRAM FOR ACTION. Illustrated. Yellow stock, 12pp.
    - SDS (org) WORKERS AND STUDENTS OPPORTUNITY TO UNITE.
    - SDS (org). DONT ISOLATE STUDENTS FROM WORKERS.CHICAGO CONSPIRACY Blue stock.
    - SDS / Radical Education Project (org). DEAR FRIEND= open letter, 8pp, + envelope.
    - SDS Asian Coalition. GREET THE AMATSVKAZE PEACE DESTROYER. IllustratedDEATH TO THE SECURITY PACT. / verso: SCHEDULE OF JAPAN WEEK ACTIVITIES.
    - SDS. SDS BANNED..ROTC MUST GO. Illustrated.
    - Student Mobilization Committee / Huelga / YSC (orgs) THE MURDER OF RUBEN SALAZARIllustrated.
    - SUPERB + Afro American Students Union (org) + Community Projects Office (org) PRESENT SUMMER SOUL WEEKincluding Afro Rags for chicks Lower Sproul Plaza. Yellow stock.
    - UC Clerical, Technical and Professional Employees, AFSCME Local 1565 / AFT Local 1570 UC Campus (org) WORK STOPPAGE / Tuesday April 9 ALL DAY
    - University of California, Berkeley / Campus Community for a Non-violent Alternative (org). TO THE REGENTSopen letter + attached statement in purple ink, The issues of the past few weeks must not be allowed to die, with sign up sheet for supporters.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Berkeley Faculty Committee (org). VIETNAM MORATORIUM-October 15, 2 leaves
    - University of California, Berkeley. English Deopt. Action Group 7. OLD, UNWANTED BOOKS? GIVE THEM TO US FOR A BOOK SALE
    - University of California, Berkeley. History Dept Steering Committee (org). NO BUSINESS AS USUAL BOYCOTT SCAB CLASSES. Tan stock.
    - University of California, Berkeley. History Dept. (org). PURPOSE OF MOBILE UNIVERSITY SEMINARS.
    - UNIVERSITY EMPLOYEES AND REVOLUTIONARIES. Red on yellow stock. Do not throw rocks until people leave the buildings.
    - West Oakland Project (org). BENEFIT. Illustrated. Ulysses Crockett & Afro-Blue Persuasion.
    - Young Socialist Alliance (org). CAMPAIGN FOR A REVOLUTIONARY CHANGE. Illustrated. 4pp.
    - Young Socialist Alliance, National Executive Committee (org). YSA PROGRAM FOR THHE CAMPUS REVOLT. Rubberstamp of the Berkeley office of the YSA. 4pp.
  - File 20 (Box 2, Folder 47-48)
    - A HUMAN EVENT FOR McCARTHY. Yellow stock.
    - AFSCME (org) NOT LIKE THIS! Cartoon. Brown stock.
    - ANARCHIST FREE ASSOCIATION. Illustrated.
    - ARTHUR SCHL:ESINGER, JR. WILL SAPEAK ON KENNEDY
    - Black Panther Party (in part) (org) PRE-ELECTION DAY PARTY. Illus. Cleaver spoke or appeared. Illustrated. Yellow stock. On verso: $100 PLATE LUNCH-IN. YIPPIE ERECTION DAY.
    - Black Panther Party (or). THE NEWTON-SEALE CAMPAIGN COMMITTEE PRESENTS Yellow stock. Panther images
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom News (Supplement) EXTRA MEETINGHUEY NEWTON FOR CONGRESS!
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Party (org) SUPPORT ELDRIDGE CLEAVER FOR PRESIDENT. Panther image.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Party (org). ELDRIDGE CLEAVER IS RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT. 4pp.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Party (org) ELDRIDGE CLEAVER IS RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT / REGISTER PEACE & FREEDOMATTEND THE P&F CONVENTION
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Party (org). FINAL MOBILIZATION.. Huey Newton a candidate for Congress.
    - Black Panther Party (org) etc. CLEAVER FOR PRESIDENT
    - Black Panther Party (org) etc. RALLYBOBBY SEALE / verso: YOU ARE NEEDED
    - Black Panther Party (org) with 9 other sponsoring groups. PROTEST OUTLAWING OF FRENCH STUDENT MOVEMENT. Illustrated
    - Black Panther Party (org). Committee on Public Safety. Cleaver. Docketed: 24 Sept 68. Another copy in Collection.
    - BRASS WANTS TO BUST OUR MARCH.
    - Campus Community for a Non-Violent Alternative (org). DEAR FACULTY MEMBER= open letter. Purple ink. 4pp + envelope.
    - Campus Friends of the Oakland 7 (org). WARNING / YOU MAY BE GUILTY OF CONSPIRACY
    - Campus Peace and Freedom (org). CONTROL OUR COPS / DEFEND FREE SPEECH
    - Campus Students for a Democratic Society Labor Committee (org). WILL YOU BE WORKING? Illustrated. Yellow stock.
    - Capitalism Stinks Vol I:1 (July 25, 1968)
    - Chamberlain (Gary) VOTE FOR IXON WITHOUT GOING TO THE POLLS!
    - CNP (org) AFTER NOV 5th WHAT? THINK APRIL! Yellow stock.
    - Committee of Responsibility (org) IN THE BAY AREA
    - Community for New Politics (org) NOV 1968THIS IS A CHOICE?
    - CPE (org) WE DESERVE CREDIT!
    - CPE (org). (dissident delegates) ORGANISE!!! THE KEY TO VICTORY
    - CPE (org). AFTER THE SENATE, WHAT NOW?
    - CPE (org).. OCCUPY THE UNIVERSITY?
    - Delaware Affinity Group (org). TREMENDOUS VICTORY
    - Democratic Women for Mulford (org) DEMOCRATS FOR MULFORD! / on verso: piece on Eldridge Cleaver
    - Dick Gregory for President Committee (org) WE NEED A NEW GOVERNMENT
    - DINO CHAVERS on orange stock.
    - Eucumenical Exchange (org). WHITE RACISM. Blue-green paper.
    - Faculty for McCarthy
    - Free Student Union of Berkeley (org) THIS WEEKNEXT WEEK
    - Grindlinger (James) THE STAKES ARE TOO HIGH
    - Heyns (Roger W.) Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. DEANS, DIRECTORS, DEPARTMENT CHAIRMEN AND FACULTY
    - Historians Committee for George McGovern (org) DEAR FELLOW HISTORIANS= open letter
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). CZECHOSLOVAKIA AND THE CRISIS IN EASTERN EUROPEtalk by Ernie Haberkern. Illustrated.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). REASON, TOLERANCE AND COPS
    - JOIN IN FORMING A RADICAL CAUCUS. Green stock.
    - Kennedy Action Corps (org) GIVE THE GHETTO THE VOTE! Orange stock. Huey Newto cited.
    - McCarthy for President Campaign (org) McCARTHY IS WINNING. Peach stock
    - McCARTHY IS WINNING.
    - McCarty for President / On To Chicago, volume 2:2 (July 22, 1968)
    - MICHAEL HARRINGTON HASNT FORGOTTEN
    - MOSES HEARINGS---JUSTICE?
    - New World Alliance SOURCE (org). TEACH IN SCHEDULE / New World Alliance
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org) RADICAL CAUCUS.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. County Council Meeting, pages 1-2. NB! Page 3 is in folder 19.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org) + CNP (campus org) WHOS GOING TO BE THE LESSER EVIL IN 68?
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org) AN EEND TO FUTILITY: Build a Real Alternative
    - Provisional Anti-Racism Com. (org). A RACIST UNIVERSITY IN A RACIST SOCIETY: An Open Letter to the Berkeley Community. Pink stock.
    - Schlesinger (Arthur, Jr.) WHY I AM FOR KENNEDY. 3 leaves.
    - SCOPE (org). VOTE SCOPE
    - SDS (Berkeley Campus Chapter) (org). WHY WE FIGHT. Yellow stock.
    - SDS (org) SUPPORT THE STRIKE AT STATE
    - SDS (org) SUPPORT THE STRIKE AT STATE
    - SDS (org) ZELLERBACH? Pink stock.
    - SDS (org). WHY WE FIGHT. Green stock.
    - SDS (Worker-student Alliance Group of Campus) (org). ANTI-COMMUNISM AT BERKELEY An Open Letter
    - SDS MEETING TUESDAY
    - SDS WHOSE STOOGE IS ROGER HEYNS?
    - SENATOR EUGENE J. McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT, 4pp
    - Socialist Action (Sept 1968)
    - SOCIALIST CANDIDATES IN 68
    - Socialist Labor Party (org). WHICH WOULD YOU CHOOSE. 4pp.
    - Socialist Voice Broadside #1, 4pp
    - Spartacist Club on Campus (org). STUDENTS AND WORKERS IN FRANCE. Orange stock.
    - SPRING / SUMMER / FALL / WINTER. Poems and prose poems, purple ink.
    - STUDENT POWER
    - Students for Meade (org) ITS TIME TO ACT. Blue stocki.
    - Students for Meade (org). WIDEN YOUR ATTENTION. Yellow stock.
    - Study Institute of Modern Oriental Philosophy (org). PRESENTS
    - SUMMER PLANNING GROUP
    - SUMMER PLANNING GROUP, docketed to be handed out
    - SUPPORT STRIKING JANITORS
    - SWOP (org) WHAT DOES SWOP HAVE TO OFFER? Pink stock. This piece is dated 25 Sept 1967, a Sproul Plaza handout.
    - TEN DAYS ARE UP
    - THE NEW YORK TIMES ON HUMPHREY. 4pp.
    - TO MEMBERS OF THE FACULTY. Dec 2, 1968. 5pp.
    - TO THE STUDENT BODY
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org) MINUTES OF THE BERKELEY DIVISION. November 26, 1968
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org) REPORT OF THE CHAIRMAN / Regents One Guest Lecture Policy.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). MINUTES OF THE BERKELEY DIVISION. October 3, 1968.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). REPORT OF THE COMMITTEEE ON SENATE POLICY / STUDENT PARTICIPATION IN SENATE AFFAIRS. 5 leaves.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). REPORTON SENATE POLICY. 11pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Dept of History (org) DEAR MR (PAUL) WARD.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Statement by Office of Public Information. 2 leaves.
    - University Bulletin17:9 (Oct 7, 1968)
    - VOTE TOM MACBRIDE / UNION PARTY / ASUC SENATE / STUDENT ECONOMIC REFORM. Orange stock.
    - Weiss (Professor David W.) UC Professor. THE ENCLOSED STATEMENT. 2 leaves
    - WHAT CAN YOU AFFORD?
    - WHEN WILL THEY EVER LEARNRead the UNION WHITE PAPER
    - WHO SAYS HE CANT WIN? McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT
    - Womens Liberation (campus org) WHERE ARE YOU GOING? Illustrated.
    - Workers Action (org) LETS GO TO WORK ON THE SYSTEM (illustrated). Yellow stock.
    - YOU CAN HELP (McCARTHY). Orange stock.
    - Young Socialists for Halstead and Boutelle (org). THE TRUTH ABOUT McCARTHY CAMPAIGN. Orange stock.
    - Phylliss work:
  - File 21 (Box 3, Folder 49-50)
    - Ad hoc Committee for Spock for President / nd
    - Ad hoc Faculty Observers Committee / 03/04/69 7pp
    - AFSCME Local 1695 / 02/26/69
    - AFT #1570 / docketed 10/24/68
    - AFT / Local 1570 02/24/69
    - Agitator no.2 / 03/10/68
    - American Association of University Professors 2pp / Diamond 06/08/67
    - Astronomy Department / docketed 10/25/68 3pp
    - Bill Miller for Mayor / 1967
    - Black and Brown Caucus of the PFP / 03/17/68
    - Black and Brown Caucus of the PFP / 03/17/68
    - Black and Brown Caucus of the PFP / nd
    - Black Panther Party / Cleaver 03/16/68 5pp
    - C.P.E. / docketed 10/14/68
    - C.P.E. / docketed 10/9/68
    - C.P.E. Coordinating Council / docketed 10/9/68
    - C.P.E. Source / docketed 10/16/68
    - Campus Friends of the AFT / 02/24/69
    - Campus Friends of the AFT 02/17/69
    - CCHC / 08/08/67
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions / 08/22/67
    - Committee of 100 / 04/67
    - Course description. New Left Forum / docketed 12/13/68
    - Declaration / Chamberlin 03/17/68
    - Department of History / Riasanovsky 10/30/68
    - Disarmament Workshop / Chamberlin 03/17/68
    - Fact Sheet / Paff 01/21/68
    - Gaustad / docketed 10/18/68
    - Instant News Service Vol. 1, No. 10 / 05/27/69
    - Instant News Service Vol. 1, No. 3 / 05/20/69
    - Interim Strike Committee / docketed 10/28/68
    - Interim Strike Committee. Strike On. / docketed 10/28/68
    - Leaflet / docketed 10/16/68
    - Leaflet / Robertson 03/01/68
    - Leaflet / Sellers docketed 10/10/68
    - Leaflet / Students in 139X docketed 10/22/68
    - Leaflet for panel discussion / docketed 10/25/68
    - Leaflet. The Resistance / nd
    - Legal System Workshop / Posey 03/16/68
    - Letter / Moore 03/16/68
    - Letter / Moore 03/16/68
    - Letter. Archibald MacLeish / Summer 1967 2pp
    - Los Angeles County Peace and Freedom Party / 03/09/68
    - Mailer / Peace and Freedom Party 01/30/68
    - Mail-in ballot / Peace and Freedom Party 05/24/68
    - Memo / docketed History Dept. Mailbox 10/28/68
    - Memo / Weinberg Nd
    - Mexican-American Confederation / docketed 10/18/68 2cc
    - Minutes. Peace & Freedom Movement / Hersh 03/22/68
    - Minutes. Peace and Freedom Movement / Fletcher 03/07/68 2pp
    - Motion / Wolin docketed 10/11/68 7pp
    - New Left Travelers / docketed 10/18/68 2cc
    - Office of the Chancellor / 10/28/68
    - Office of the Chancellor / Boyd 11/13/67
    - Office of the Chancellor / Cheit 11/14/67
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 10/24/68 3pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Searcy 07/31/67 2pp
    - Peace and Freedom Candidates / 02/15/68
    - Peace and Freedom Movement Agenda / 02/15/68
    - Peace and Freedom News / 03/12/68
    - Peace and Freedom News Issues I & II / 03/12/68
    - Peace and Freedom Party / 01/30/68
    - Peace and Freedom Party / 01/31/68
    - Peace and Freedom Party / Mack. nd
    - Peace and Freedom Party Press Release / 02/08/68
    - Peace and Freedom Party Statement / nd
    - Peace and Freedom Party. Proposals / nd
    - Peace and Freedom Party. Proposals / nd 24pp
    - Peace and Freedom Party. Riverside County Convention / 03/02/68 2pp
    - Peace and Freedom Party. Riverside County Convention / nd
    - Peace and Freedom Party. Riverside County Council / nd
    - Peace and Freedom Party. San Mateo County Convention / 02/25/68
    - Plaza handout docketed / 03/01/67
    - Press Release / 10/17/72 (docketed 10/22/68)
    - Proposal / Schachter 03/18/68
    - Rally Leaflet. Peace & Freedom Movement / docketed 11/05/68
    - Report / Denman 01/27/68
    - Resolution / Edmond. nd
    - Resolution. Peace and Freedom Party. Placer County Convention / nd
    - Resolution. Peace and Freedom Party. Sonoma County Convention / nd
    - Sacramento County Peace and Freedom Party Platform / nd
    - SDS / docketed 10/16/68
    - SDS / docketed 10/29/68
    - SDS Support the Strike / docketed 10/28/68
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns docketed 10/30/68
    - Statements of Candidates / 04/04/67
    - Strike Rally Leaflet / docketed 11/06/68
    - Striking Students / docketed 10/25/68
    - Students for Meade / docketed 10/18/68
    - Students for Meade / docketed 10/22/68
    - The New York Times. Reprint / 06/08/67
    - Third World Liberation Front / 02/21/69
    - Third World Liberation Front / 02/26/69
    - Third World Liberation Front. Communique #10 / 02/26/69
    - UC Division of the Senate / Kip 04/28/67
    - University Young Democrats / 03/01/67 docketed
    - Vote Socialist flier / Camejo 11/05/68
    - Vote Socialist flier / Camejo nd
    - Workshops map / nd
    - Yolo County Peace and Freedom Party / nd
  - File 22 (Box 3, Folder 51-52)
    - Academic Senate Berkeley Division / Powell 10/11/69
    - Academic Senate / Powell 03/12/69
    - AFSCME / docketed 11/06/69
    - AFT Local 1474 / 02/26/69
    - AFT-TWLF / nd
    - Anonymous faculty members UCB / docketed 10/13/69
    - Arab Student Association / docketed 10/10/69
    - Arab Student Association. Poem / docketed 10/10/69
    - Arab Students Union / docketed 10/27/69
    - ASUC and Third World Liberation Front / 04/12/69
    - ASUC Leaflet / docketed 06/24/69
    - ASUC Leaflet / docketed 10/29/69
    - Bay Area Peace Action Council / docketed 11/09/69
    - Bay Council on Soviet Jewry / Light 10/08/09
    - Bay Council on Soviet Jewry / Light 10/10/69
    - Berkeley Defense Committee / docketed 10/09/69
    - Berkeley Defense Committee / docketed 10/10/69
    - Berkeley Defense Committee / docketed 10/15/69
    - Berkeley Faculty Letter / 08/13/69
    - Berkeley Faculty Union / docketed 11/05/69
    - Berkeley Faculty Vietnam Organizing Committee / 09/02/69
    - Berkeley Society of Friends / 05/26/69
    - Berkeley Tenants Union / 10/10/69
    - Berkeley Tenants Union / docketed 10/08/69
    - Berkeley Tenants Union / docketed 11/03/69
    - Campus Crusade for Christ / docketed 10/27/69
    - Campus Crusade for Christ / docketed 10/27/69
    - Campus Friends of the AFT / 02/17/69
    - Campus Independent Socialist Club / nd
    - Campus SDS / docketed 10/28/69
    - Campus SDS / docketed 10/29/69
    - Christian World Liberation Front / docketed 10/08/69
    - Christian World Liberation Front / docketed 10/15/69
    - Christian World Liberation Front / docketed 10/27/69
    - Committee on Academic Freedom / 10/07/69
    - Committee on Liberation or Death / 10/14/69
    - Faculty Exchange. U.S. Court of Appeals / nd
    - FLF / docketed 10/08/69
    - Golden Gate Free University / nd
    - History Department / 01/23/69
    - International Liberation School / docketed 10/24/69
    - International Socialists / 10/15/69
    - Into the New Age Committee / docketed 11/06/69
    - Leaflet / docketed 04/17/70
    - Leaflet / docketed 10/09/69
    - Letter / Campbell 01/21/69
    - Letter / Jenner 01/23/69
    - Letter / Jenner 08/22/69
    - Letter / Mandel 01/09/69
    - Letter / Sealey 01/10/69
    - NAACP / 02/04/69
    - New Mobilization Committee / docketed 10/27/69
    - NUC Newsletter Vol. III, No. 1 / 08/15/69
    - NUC Newsletter Vol. III, No. 4 / 10/01/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / 10/13/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Bouwsma 02/06/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Bouwsma 02/06/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/05/69
    - Panel discussion Leaflet / docketed 11/06/69
    - Peoples Park Negotiating Committee / nd
    - Radical Student Union / 03/13/69
    - Radical Student Union / 03/13/69
    - Radical Student Union / docketed 11/03/69
    - Radical Student Union / docketed 11/03/69
    - Radical Student Union / docketed 11/04/69
    - Radical Student Union / docketed 11/06/69
    - Radical Student Union / docketed 11/06/69
    - Rally poster / docketed 11/06/69
    - Rally poster / docketed 11/10/69
    - Right On. Newspaper / docketed 10/27/69
    - RSU Labor Commission / docketed 10/10/69
    - RSU Labor Committee / docketed 06/03/69
    - S.M.C. Vietnam Moratorium / docketed 10/30/69
    - Schedule of events. Vietnam Moratorium Committee / docketed 10/14/69
    - Scientists and Engineers Against War Research / nd
    - SDS / docketed 10/29/69
    - SDS / docketed 11/03/69
    - SDS / Sargeant, Gordon, et al. docketed 10/14/69
    - SMC / docketed 11/3/69
    - Society for Universal Communication and Knowledge / docketed 10/10/69
    - Stamler / 08/25/69
    - Strike. Leaflet. / docketed 10/30/69
    - Student Mobilization Committee / docketed 10/28/69
    - Student Mobilization Committee / docketed 11/03/69
    - Students for New Age Unification / docketed 10/29/69
    - The Sun Reporter / 10/25/69
    - Third World Liberation Front 02/26/69
    - UC Department of English / 02/15/69
    - UC Office of the Dean / 03/11/69
    - United Scoopers Union / docketed 10/08/69
    - University Bulletin / 02/10/69
    - University Librarian / Skipper 02/14/69
    - Vietnam Moratorium / nd
    - Vietnam Moratorium Committee / docketed 10/09/69
    - Vietnam Moratorium Committee / docketed 10/14/69
    - Vietnam Moratorium Student Committee / docketed 10/14/69
    - Wesley Foundation / 10/30/69
    - WFP / docketed 11/03/69
    - World Without War / Pickus 10/05/69
    - Young Peoples Socialist League / docketed 10/24/69
  - File 23 (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
    - Set Bobby Free Leaflet / nd
    - Academic Senate / 05/23/69
    - Academic Senate / Cockrell 11/17/69
    - Academic Senate / Heyman 02/20/69
    - Academic Senate / Powell 10/11/69
    - Academic Senate. Notice of Meeting / 11/10/69
    - Academic Senate. Notice of Meeting / 11/24/69
    - Active Conservation / nd
    - Ad hoc Faculty Observers Committee / 03/04/69
    - AFL-CIO Employee Press / 01/29/69
    - AFSCME Local 1695 / 02/26/69
    - AFSCME. Rally. 02/25/69
    - AFT 1570 / Pamphlet nd
    - AFT Berkeley / nd
    - AFT Local 1352 / 01/17/69
    - AFT Local 1352 / nd
    - AFT Local 1474 / 02/26/69
    - AFT Local 1474 / nd
    - AFT Local 1570 / 03/17/69
    - ASUC / Huen 10/01/69
    - Bay Area Peace Action Committee / nd
    - Bay Area Spartacist League / 05/06/70
    - Berkeley Co-op / nd
    - CAC Pamphlet / nd
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 / 02/24/69
    - Campus Independent Socialist Club / nd
    - Center for Educational Change / 11/20/69
    - Center for Educational Change / docketed 10/23/69
    - Citizens Against Legalized Murder / nd
    - Department of History / 07/17/69
    - Department of History / Riasanovsky 03/03/69
    - Department of History / Riasanovsky 03/12/69
    - Faculty Committee for Human Rights in El Salvador / nd
    - Faculty Exchange / White 01/22/69
    - First Congregational Church / 10/15/69
    - International Longshoremens Union / Bridges 12/01/69
    - International Socialists / docketed 12/10/69
    - Iranian Students Association / 10/21/69
    - IWW Pamphlet / nd
    - Kiel Newsletter / 12/21/68
    - Leaflet / Whitman 04/25/69
    - Leaflet. Public Assembly / 03/15/69
    - Leaflet. Stop the war / nd
    - Letter / AFL-CIO 10/14/69
    - Letter / Barnes 09/18/69
    - Letter / Blauner 10/14/69
    - Letter / Buxbaum 03/03/69
    - Letter / Dizard and Wellman 09/01/68 2pp
    - Letter / Scriven. nd
    - Letter, AFL-CIO 06/10/69 2cc
    - National Farm Workers Association / Chatfield 03/01/66
    - National Lawyers Guild / Duga 04/22/69
    - NUC Newsletter Vol. III, No. 3 / 09/15/69
    - NUC The Radical Teacher / 09/01/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / 10/03/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Bouwsma 02/19/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Connick 10/13/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 01/17/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/01/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/24/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/25/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 04/01/69
    - Office of the Registrar / 03/01/69
    - Peace and Freedom News / 01/31/69
    - Peace and Freedom News / 02/28/69
    - Peoples Park Commencement Committee / nd 2cc
    - Position paper / Brown, Brunner, et al. / nd
    - Record. Academic Senate / 11/03/69
    - Report / Searle 03/03/69
    - Report. Academic Freedom Committee / 11/11/69
    - Report. Academic Freedom Committee / 11/11/69
    - Report. Academic Senate / 02/24/69
    - Report. Academic Senate / 03/04/69
    - Report. Academic Senate / 05/23/69
    - Report. Academic Senate / Powell 09/20/69
    - Resolution. Academic Senate / 11/10/69
    - Rip Off / RSU 02/28/69
    - Scientists and Engineers Against War Research / 06/06/69
    - SDS News / nd
    - SF Mime Troupe / nd
    - SF Socialist Summer School / nd
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 07/15/69
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 01/23/69
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/19/69
    - Strike Committee. Strike Suspended. / nd
    - Student Mobilization Committee / docketed 12/11/69
    - Telegraph Avenue Liberation Front / 09/19/69
    - Telegraph Avenue Summer Program / 06/06/69 2cc
    - Third World Faculty Alliance / 03/04/69
    - Third World Liberation Front / nd
    - Tract / Osterhus Publishing nd
    - TWLF / 02/26/69
    - TWLF Communique #2 / 03/03/69
    - UC Academic Senate. Minutes of the Berkeley Division / 02/03/69
    - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee / 11/13/69
    - University Bulletin / 02/24/69
    - University Bulletin / 03/03/69
    - University Bulletin / 03/10/69
    - Vietnam Moratorium Committee / nd
    - Workers for Peoples Democracy / 11/01/69
  - File 24 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
    - AFSCME Local 1695 / nd
    - AFT Local 1474 / Freeman nd
    - AFT Local 1474 Berkeley Faculty Union / Steinhardt nd
    - American Students for Israel / nd
    - Anti-war Coalition / nd
    - Barb on Strike leaflet / nd
    - Bay Area Peace Action Council / nd
    - Bay Area Spartacist League / nd
    - Bumper sticker / nd
    - Butchers Union / nd
    - C.P.E. Coordinating Council / docketed Cleaver
    - C.P.E. Course enrollment / nd